So if you are black and you genuinely want to see change in this nation and you have identified as a Democrat thus far, I want to offer you the opportunity to take in some new information that I believe is integral to actually being an effective tool for the change you wish to see.
If you are curious about this, then please drop, tell me more in the comments.
This will let me know if this is something that I really should set up because I see a lot of black people who I believe really earnestly want to see change.
However, they are lacking some really vital information that is not put out there and it's not put out there for a reason.
It's not put out there because we're enough people to really know that information.
Then it would force certain factions to behave differently that ultimately do not want to.
So if you are curious and you would like me to do a free information session that tells you about the things that I learned that have really been a blessing to expanding my knowledge and empowering my capability for a change,
then please drop, then please drop, tell me more in the comments.
If I get a minimum of 50 tell me mores, I will put together an information session that will let you be a part of a conversation that hopefully will begin or at least extend the necessary coalition that we need to build.
For the record, Ops, I expect you to show up.
I wouldn't expect anything else.
Please know that we do know that you will be there.
So, welcome.